A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation photographs FA003
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States - General
  - Representative Government in Europe Conference (Box 25, Folder 677)
  - Pan American Sanitary Bureau - Building Purchase (Box 25, Folder 678)
  - Pan American Sanitary Conference - Brazil (Box 25, Folder 679)
    Dinners, conferences, group portraits.
  - People's Institute NYC (Box 25, Folder 680)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy - Remedial Education (Box 25, Folder 681)
    Students, teachers, group portraits.
  - Population Council (Box 25, Folder 682)
    Laboratories, animal testing.
  - Population Council - Family Planning - Survey in Pakistan (Box 25, Folder 683)
  - Population Council - Technical Assistance - Korea (Box 25, Folder 684)
    Birth control, Korea, family planning.
  - Population Council - Technical Assistance - Taiwan (Box 25, Folder 685)
    Birth control, family planning, Taiwan.
  - Population Council - Technical Assistance - Taiwan (Box 25, Folder 686)
    Birth control, Taiwan, family planning.
  - Population Council - Reference Bureau - Latin American Program (Box 26, Folder 687)
  - Princeton University - Population Research (Box 26, Folder 688)
  - Princeton University - Remedial Education (Box 26, Folder 689)
    Arts, students, classrooms.
  - Public Administration Clearing House (Box 26, Folder 690)
  - Research Foundations Inc. (Box 26, Folder 691)
    Laboratories, supply rooms, observatories.
  - Rockefeller Center (Box 26, Folder 692)
    Aerial views, New York, Rockefeller Center.
  - Sabin, A (Box 26, Folder 693)
  - Spectroscope (Box 26, Folder 694)
  - Stanford University - Food Research Institute in Africa (Box 26, Folder 695)
    Villages, farmers, indigenous people, Africa.
  - Stanley, W. (Box 26, Folder 696)
  - Tulane University (Box 26, Folder 697)
    Schools, grounds, buildings.
  - Truman Library (Box 26, Folder 698)
    Libraries, construction, aerial views.
  - Tuskegee Insitute (Box 26, Folder 711)
  - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute (Box 26, Folder 712)
    Iraq, Palestine.
  - University of North Carolina - Medical Practice (Box 26, Folder 713)
    Doctors, home visits.
  - University of Pittsburgh - Radiation (Box 26, Folder 714)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 26, Folder 715)
    Children, medical exams.
  - Vanderbilt University (Box 26, Folder 716)
    Schools, buildings, grounds.
  - Vanderbilt University - Nutrition (Box 26, Folder 717)
    Schools, offices, laboratories.
  - Webster Springs Community Building (Box 26, Folder 718)
    Buildings, construction.
  - WHO - Experts Committee on Radiation (Box 26, Folder 719)
  - WNET (Box 26, Folder 720)
    Public television, theatre, productions.
  - World Student Service Fund (Box 26, Folder 721)
  - YMCA College, Chicago (Box 26, Folder 722)
  - American Bureau For Medical Aid to China (Box 27, Folder 699)
  - American Film Center - Medical Films (Box 27, Folder 700)
    Motion pictures.
  - American Psychiatric Association - Mental Hospital Design (Box 27, Folder 701)
    Meetings, group portraits, hospitals, mental health, plans, designs.
  - Behavior Research Fund - Area Project (Box 27, Folder 702)
    Children, boys clubs, recreation.
  - Bradley Home (Box 27, Folder 703)
  - Catholic University Psychiatry (Box 27, Folder 704)
  - Child Research Council, Denver (Box 27, Folder 705)
    Children, medical exams, medical tests.
  - Columbia University - Reproductive Biology (Box 27, Folder 706)
    Swine, animals, laboratories.
  - Columbia University - Psychiatry - Waelsch (Box 27, Folder 707)
  - Columbia University - Sex Research (Box 27, Folder 708)
    Monkeys, animal testing, surgery.
  - Committee on Research in Medical Economics (Box 27, Folder 709)
    Books
  - Cornell University - Reflex Behavior (Box 27, Folder 710)
    Animals, sheep, animal testing, testing facilities.
  - Dartmouth College - Physiological Optics (Box 27, Folder 723)
  - Duke University - Parapsychology (Box 27, Folder 724)
  - Duke University - Psychology (Box 27, Folder 725)
    Medical exams, testing, laboratories, schools, grounds.
  - Education Council for Foreigh Medical Graduates (Box 27, Folder 726)
    Interviews, doctors. offices.
  - Georgia State College For Women - Genetics (Box 27, Folder 727)
    Animals, mice, women, schools.
  - Harvard University - Epilepsy (Box 27, Folder 729)
    Children, medical exams, testing, laboratories, diseases, epilepsy.
  - Harvard University - Legal Medicine (Box 27, Folder 730)
    Laboratories, schools.
  - Harvard University Library (Box 27, Folder 731)
  - Harvard University - Navaho Indian Study (Box 27, Folder 732)
    Native Americans, families, covered wagons.
  - Harvard University - Physiology (Box 27, Folder 733)
    Books, libraries.
  - Jackson Memorial Laboratory - Genetics (Box 27, Folder 734)
    Dogs, training, kennels, animal testing, animals.
  - Johns Hopkins University - Insititute of the History of Medicine (Box 27, Folder 735)
    Group portraits, exhibitions.
  - Johns Hopkins University - Psychiatry (Box 27, Folder 736)
    Buildings, psychiatry, children.
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Medicine (Box 27, Folder 737)
    Hospitals, doctors.
  - Judge Baker Guidance Center (Box 27, Folder 738)
    Children, recreation.
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Psychiatry (Box 27, Folder 739)
    Patients, medical exams.
  - McLean Hospital - Bilain Chemistry (Box 27, Folder 740)
    Laboratories, doctors, hospitals.
  - Meharry Medical College - General Support (Box 27, Folder 741)
    Hospitals, medical exams, children, infants, pediatrics, dentistry.
  - National Committee on Maternal Health (Box 27, Folder 742)
  - New York University - Physiology (Box 28, Folder 743)
  - New York University - Radiation Hazards (Box 28, Folder 744)
    Radiation, equipment.
  - New York University - Rehabilitation (Box 28, Folder 745)
    Rehabilitation, medical exams, patients.
  - Pennsylvania Hopital - Psychiatry (Box 28, Folder 746)
    Medical exams, patients.
  - Pennsylvania State College - Nutrition Study (Box 28, Folder 747)
  - Post Graduate Medical Institute - Exhibit (Box 28, Folder 748)
    Exhibits
  - Princeton University - Psychology of Perseption (Box 28, Folder 749)
    Experiments
  - St. Luke's Hospital - City Nutrition (Box 28, Folder 750)
    Laboratories, hospitals.
  - Southwestern Medical School - Microscopy (Box 28, Folder 751)
    Laboratories, equipment, microscopy.
  - Tufts College - Brain Chemistry (Box 28, Folder 752)
    Laboratories
  - Tulane University - Foreign Trainee Program (Box 28, Folder 753)
  - Tulane University - Legal Medicine (Box 28, Folder 754)
  - United States Medical Education (Box 28, Folder 755)
    Military, wards.
  - United States Army Medical Library (Box 28, Folder 756)
    Libraries, equipment.
  - University of Chicago - Psychology (Box 28, Folder 757)
    Offices
  - University of Illinois - Neurology (Box 28, Folder 758)
    Hospitals, builldings.
  - University of Minnesota - Human Genetics (Box 28, Folder 759)
    Genetics
  - University of North Carolina - Dermatology (Box 28, Folder 760)
  - University of Oregon - Constitutional Medicine (Box 28, Folder 761)
    Exams, patients.
  - University of Pennsylvania - Dermatology (Box 28, Folder 762)
    Hospitals, diseases, ringworm, patients, children, medical exams, laboratories.
  - University of Pennsylvania - Dermatology (Box 28, Folder 764)
  - University of Tennessee - Psychiatry (Box 28, Folder 765)
    Therapy, patients, hospitals.
  - Vanderbilt University - Medical School (Box 28, Folder 767)
    Buildings, schools.
  - Yale University - Neuroanatomy (Box 28, Folder 768)
    Equipment
  - Yale University - Endocrinology (Box 28, Folder 769)
    Equipment, laboratories.
  - Simmons College (Box 28, Folder 770)
  - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing (Box 28, Folder 771)
    Schools, buildings, nurses, patients, students, classrooms.
  - Visiting Nurse Association of Rochester - Phillips (Box 28, Folder 772)
    Group portrait, nurses.
  - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal (Box 28, Folder 773)
    Microfilm, equipment.
  - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas - Animal Nutritition (Box 28, Folder 774)
    Machinery
  - Duke University - Physical Chemistry (Box 28, Folder 775)
  - Drosophila Stock Center (Box 28, Folder 776)
    Laboratories, Cold Spring Harbor.
  - Field Museum Natural History - Chicago - Permanent Historical Record (Box 28, Folder 777)
    Plants
  - Harvard University - Chemistry (Box 28, Folder 778)
  - Harvard University - Mt. Washington Station (Box 28, Folder 779)
    Weather stations.
  - Harvard University - Physical Chemistry (Box 28, Folder 780)
  - Iowa State College - Nematodes (Box 29, Folder 781)
    Laboratories, equipment, specimines.
  - Jackson Memorial Laboratory - Genetics (Box 29, Folder 782)
    Kennels, animals, dogs.
  - Duke University - Forestry (Box 29, Folder 783)
    Forestry
  - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Cellulose (Box 29, Folder 784)
    Plants, specimines.
  - California Institute of Technology - Mt. Wilson (Box 29, Folder 785)
    Glass, furnaces, machinery.
  - California Institute of Technology - Plant Physiology (Box 29, Folder 786)
    Plants, laboratories, testing.
  - Catholic Relief Services - Brazilian Model Farm (Box 29, Folder 787)
    Farming, corn, schools, irrigation.
  - Clemson Agricultural College - Clover Fungi (Box 29, Folder 788)
  - Columbia University - Enzyme Chemistry (Box 29, Folder 789)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experimental Station - Plant Growth (Box 29, Folder 790)
    Corn
  - Conservation Foundation (Box 29, Folder 791)
    Oil, refineries.
  - Cornell University - Agriculture (Box 30, Folder 792)
    Agriculture, corn.
  - Cornell University - Agriculture Orientation Program (Box 30, Folder 793)
  - Cornell University - Nutrition (Box 30, Folder 794)
    Animals, animal testing, experiments, laboratories.
  - Indiana University - Cytogenetics (Box 30, Folder 795)
    Laboratories, tests.
  - Jackson Memorial Lab. - Genetics (Box 30, Folder 796)
    Laboratories, tests, dogs.
  - Johns Hopkins University - Nutrition (Box 30, Folder 797)
    Swine
  - Johns Hopkins University - Biochemistry (Box 30, Folder 798)
    Plants, laboratories.
  - Kansas State College - Grain Storage (Box 30, Folder 799)
  - Louisiana State University - Rice Center (Box 30, Folder 800)
    Rice, farming, machinery.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory - Woods Hole (Box 30, Folder 801)
    Sharks, sealife, buildings, libraries.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory - Woods Hole (Box 30, Folder 802)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Crystallography (Box 31, Folder 803)
    Equipment, cameras.
  - New York University - Enzyme Chemistry (Box 31, Folder 804)
    Laboratories, experiments.
  - New York Zoological Society - Marine Biology (Box 31, Folder 805)
    Sealife, dolfins.
  - Oberlin College - Science Building (Box 31, Folder 806)
  - Oceanic Foundation - Fish Culture Laboratory (Box 31, Folder 807)
    Seascapes
  - Oceanic Foundation - Fish Culture Laboratory (Box 31, Folder 808)
    Slides
  - Pan American Sanitary Bureau (Box 31, Folder 809)
    Argentina, offices, buildings.
  - Peabody Foundation For Archaeology (Box 31, Folder 810)
    Archaeology, excavations.
  - Pennsylvania State College - X-Ray Crystallography (Box 31, Folder 811)
    X-rays, equipment.
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn - Protein Structure (Box 31, Folder 812)
  - Prudue University - Genetics (Box 31, Folder 813)
    Laboratories, poultry.
  - Purdue University - Plant Physiology (Box 32, Folder 814)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (Box 32, Folder 815)
    Slide specimines.
  - Rutgers University - Animal Behavior (Box 32, Folder 816)
    Animals, laboratories, animal testing.
  - Smith College - Plant Genetics (Box 32, Folder 817)
    Conferences, group portraits.
  - Stanford University - Natural Product Chemistry (Box 32, Folder 818)
    Laboratories, group portraits.
  - United States Department of Agriculture - Poultry Research (Box 32, Folder 819)
    Farming
  - University of Arizona - Arid Lands (Box 32, Folder 820)
    Archaeology, excavations, plants, greenhouses, aerial views.
  - University of Arizona - Arid Lands (Box 32, Folder 821)
  - University of California - Hormone Research (Box 32, Folder 822)
  - University of California - Oceanography (Box 33, Folder 823)
    Oceanography, equiment, sealions, dolphins.
  - University of California - Oceanography (Box 33, Folder 824)
  - University of California - Oceanography (Box 33, Folder 825)
  - University of California - White Mountain Station (Box 33, Folder 826)
    Landscapes, mountain ranges.
  - University of Florida - Latin America Program (Box 33, Folder 827)
  - University of Illinois - Dairy Science (Box 33, Folder 828)
    Animals, cows, animal testing, laboratories.
  - University of Miami - Marine Laboratory (Box 33, Folder 829)
    Boats, oceanography.
  - University of Minnesota - Plant Research (Box 34, Folder 830)
    Plants, laboratories, greenhouses, group portraits.
  - University of Missouri - Genetics (Box 34, Folder 831)
    Buildings
  - University of Virginia - Enzyme Chemistry (Box 34, Folder 832)
  - University of Washington - Biochemistry (Box 34, Folder 833)
  - University of Wisconsin - Enzyme Research (Box 34, Folder 834)
    Buildings, laboratories.
  - University of Wisconsin - Cytogenetics (Box 34, Folder 835)
    Laboratories, plants.
  - University of Wisconsin - Genetics (Box 34, Folder 836)
  - University of Wisconsin - Physical Chemistry (Box 34, Folder 837)
    Machinery, equipment.
  - Washington State College - Agriculture (Box 34, Folder 838)
    Farming, machinery, equipment, agriculture.
  - University of Wisconsin - Potato Research (Box 34, Folder 839)
  - University of Wisconsin - Solar Energy (Box 35, Folder 840)
    Energy, experiments.
  - Volunteers for International Technical Assistance (Box 35, Folder 841)
    Energy, equipment.
  - Von Koenigswald (Box 35, Folder 842)
    Anthropology, archaelogy, portraits.
  - Weidenreich, F (Box 35, Folder 843)
  - Washington State College - Agriculture (Box 35, Folder 844)
  - Yale University - Protein Chemistry (Box 35, Folder 845)
  - Yale University - Anthropoid Research, 1 (Box 35, Folder 846)
    Animals, animal testing, experiments, monkeys.
  - Yale University - Anthropoid Research, 2 (Box 35, Folder 847)
  - (Box 35, Folder 848)
  - Cornell Latin American Year (CLAY) (Box 35, Folder 849)
  - University of California Cancer Control (Box 35, Folder 850)
  - Hookworm Conference - Richmond (Box 35, Folder 851)
    Group portraits, diseases, hookworm, specimines.
  - Hookworm Dispensaries - North Carolina (Box 35, Folder 852)
    Hookworm, diseases, group portraits, clinics.
  - Stills - Subject - Discussion of Dr. Ferrell's Circular Letters November 1914 (Box 35, Folder 853)
    Hookworm, diseases, privys.
  - County Health Unit - Kentucky (Box 35, Folder 854)
    Group portrits, clinics.
  - Johns Hopkins University - Mental Health (Box 35, Folder 855)
    Children
  - Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 856)
    Children, group portraits, laboratories.
  - Provincial Exhibition - Demonstration Booth - Quebec City (Box 35, Folder 857)
    Exhibits, medical.
  - Johns Hopkins University - Training Area (Box 35, Folder 858)
    Medical exams, medical training, pediatrics, children.
  - Harvard University - Sanitary Engineering (Box 35, Folder 859)
  - Harvard University - School of Public Health (Box 36, Folder 860)
  - Johns Hopkins University - School of Hygiene and Public Health (Box 36, Folder 861)
    Group portraits
  - Abraham Lincoln Association (Box 36, Folder 862)
    Libraries, archives, archival manuscripts.
  - Actors Studio Inc. (Box 36, Folder 863)
    Theater, performance arts.
  - Actors Studio, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 864)
    Theater, performing arts
  - Alaska Festival of Music (Box 36, Folder 865)
    Music, performing arts, orchestras.
  - Edward Albee (Box 36, Folder 866)
  - American Council of Learned Societies 1938 - Far Eastern Studies (Box 36, Folder 867)
  - American Council of Learned Societies 1938 - Latin American Handbook (Box 36, Folder 868)
    Books, Latin America.
  - American Council of Learned Societies 1941 (Box 36, Folder 869)
  - American Council of Learned Societies 1951 - Personnel in Humanities (Box 36, Folder 870)
  - American Council of Learned Societies 1950 - Slavic Studies (Box 36, Folder 871)
  - American Council of Learned Societies 1943 - Univ. of Vermont (Box 36, Folder 872)
  - American Council of Learned Societies - Korean Studies (Box 36, Folder 873)
    Portrait
  - American Council of Learned Societies - Modern Language (Box 36, Folder 874)
    Military, languages, training
  - American Foundation for the Blind (Box 36, Folder 875)
    Theater, performance arts, children, disabilities.
  - American Foundation for the Blind - Drama (Box 36, Folder 876)
    Theater, performing arts, Children, disabilities.
  - American Library Association (Box 36, Folder 877)
    Libraries, books, equipment, reprographics, exhibits.
  - American Place Theater (Box 36, Folder 878)
  - American Shakespeare Festival (Box 36, Folder 879)
    Theater, performing arts, construction.
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1959 (Box 36, Folder 880)
    Group portraits, performing arts, orchestras, theater.
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1956 (Box 36, Folder 881)
    Group portraits, performing arts, orchestras.
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (Box 36, Folder 882)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (Box 36, Folder 883)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1957 (Box 36, Folder 884)
    Performing arts, theater, orchestras.
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1958 (Box 37, Folder 885)
    Orchestras, theater, performing arts.
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1958 (Box 37, Folder 886)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League 1958 (Box 37, Folder 887)
  - ANTA - Hungarian Refugees (Box 37, Folder 888)
    Performing arts.
  - Antioch College - General Education (Box 37, Folder 889)
    Schools, students, teachers, children.
  - Arena Stage - Washington (Box 37, Folder 890)
    Theater, performing arts, buildings.
  - Barnard College - Electronic Music (Box 37, Folder 891)
    Music, equipment.
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra - Berkshire Music Center (Box 37, Folder 892)
    Theaters, orchestras, performing arts.
  - Brooklyn Museum (Box 37, Folder 893)
    Museums, arts, exhibits, galleries.
  - Brown University - English Language Teaching in Egypt (Box 37, Folder 894)
    Language, instruction.
  - Buffalo Museum of Science (Box 37, Folder 895)
    Art, exhibits, galleries, museums, Americana, Native Americans, animals, science, group portraits.
  - Carolina Art Association - Dock Street Theater, Gibbes Memorial Art Gallery (Box 37, Folder 896)
    Art, exhibits, galleries, museums, theaters.
  - Children's Museeum Survey (Box 37, Folder 897)
  - Chinese History (Box 37, Folder 898)
    Group portraits, meetings.
  - Claremont Colleges (Box 37, Folder 899)
    Libraries, arts, weaving.
  - Colorado School of Mines - English Language Teaching (Box 37, Folder 900)
    Language, instruction, schools.
  - Columbia University - Electronic Music (Box 37, Folder 901)
  - Congress of Strings - By the American Federation of Musicians (Box 37, Folder 902)
    Music, orchestras, performing arts.
  - Converse College - Brevand Music Center (Box 37, Folder 903)
  - Cornell University - Drama (Box 37, Folder 904)
    Theater, drama, performing arts.
  - Cowell, Henry 1956 (Box 37, Folder 905)
    Portraits
  - Cowell, Henry (Box 37, Folder 906)
    Korea, Ceylon, group portraits, indiginous peoples.
  - Curtis Institute of Music - GRAF (Box 37, Folder 907)
    Arenas, theaters, drama, performing arts.
  - Dallas Theater Center (Box 37, Folder 908)
    Theater, performing arts, drama.
  - Educational Braodcasting Corportation (Box 37, Folder 909)
    Group portraits, television.
  - Elma Lewis School of Fine Arts (Box 37, Folder 910)
    Dance, performing arts, schools, children.
  - Foundation for American Dance - Joffrey Ballet (Box 37, Folder 911)
  - Gest Chinese Research Library (Box 37, Folder 912)
    Libraries
  - Goethe Bicentennial Foundation (Box 37, Folder 913)
    Ceremonies
  - Harvard University - Confluence - Richards - Slavic Studies (Box 38, Folder 914)
    Language instruction, schools, classrooms.
  - Hofstra College - Scenery Mechanics (Box 38, Folder 915)
    Theater, machinery, equipment.
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts - Ryukyu Cultural Reconnaissance (Box 38, Folder 916)
    Art, Sculpture, tapestry, exhibits, galleries.
  - Hoover War Memorial Library (Box 38, Folder 917)
    Libraries, memorials, buildings.
  - Houston Symphony Orchestra - Young Composers Program (Box 38, Folder 918)
    Models, buildings.
  - Humanities in Print, the (Box 38, Folder 919)
    Books, displays.
  - Indiana University - East European Studies - Latin American Music - Thai Art (Box 38, Folder 921)
    Arts, sculpture, exhibits, museums.
  - Institute For Advanced Studies in the Theater Arts (Box 38, Folder 922)
    Performing arts, yheater, drama.
  - Institute of International Education - Student Artist Exchange (Box 38, Folder 923)
    Arts, dance, drama, painting, group portraits.
  - Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 38, Folder 924)
  - International Graphic Arts Society - Print Lending Program (Box 38, Folder 925)
    Arts, exhibits, galleries.
  - Ithaca Festival of the Classics (Box 38, Folder 926)
    Theaters, buildings.
  - Karamu House - de Souza - Music Building (Box 38, Folder 927)
    Performing arts, theater, drama.
  - Kenyon College (Box 38, Folder 928)
    Publications, offices.
  - Laban, Juanade (Box 38, Folder 929)
  - Library of Congress (Box 38, Folder 930)
    Buildings, libraries, archives, equipment, microphotography.
  - Lincoln Center (Box 38, Folder 931)
    Performing arts, theaters, construction, models, buildings, designs.
  - Little Symphony Society (Box 38, Folder 932)
    Orchestras, performing arts, music.
  - Marlboro Music Festival (Box 38, Folder 933)
    Orchestras, music, performing arts.
  - Louisville Philharmonic Society (Box 38, Folder 934)
    Performing arts, music, orchestras.
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - DUCA (Box 38, Folder 935)
    Sculpture, casting, arts.
  - Minneapolis Institute of Arts - Children's Theater Company (Box 38, Folder 936)
  - Minnesota Theater Company Foundation - Voice Teachers Training (Box 38, Folder 937)
    Instruction, voice.
  - Museums - Yellowstone Park (Box 38, Folder 938)
    Museums, national parks, buildings.
  - Museum of Costume Art - Johnson (Box 38, Folder 939)
    Costumes, drama, theater.
  - Museum of Modern Art - Film Library (Box 38, Folder 940)
  - National Archives and Records Administration - Microfilm (Box 38, Folder 941)
    Microphotography, libraries, equipment.
  - National Cultural Center (Box 38, Folder 942)
    Buildings, models, designs.
  - National Educational Television - Regional Theater (Box 38, Folder 943)
    Television, performing arts.
  - National Repertory Theater (Box 38, Folder 944)
  - National Repertory Theater Foundation (Box 39, Folder 945)
    Portraits, performers, actors.
  - National Theater Conference (Box 39, Folder 946)
    Drama, performing arts, theater.
  - Nelson Gallery of Art (Box 39, Folder 947)
    Art, sculpture, painting, Colonial Williamsburg, Egyptian, Indian.
  - New Dramatists Committee, Inc. - General Support (Box 39, Folder 948)
    Group portraits, drama, theater, performing arts.
  - New York City Center - Kabuki Troupe (Box 39, Folder 949)
    Drama, theater, performing arts, Asia, Kabuki.